const scope = [
    {
    "question": "What type of data do you expect when you console.log(2 in [1,2])?",
    "options":["String", "Number", "Boolean", "Undefined"],
    "answer" : "Boolean",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "What do you expect when you console.log(2 in [4,5,8])?",
    "options":["False", "8", "True", "Undefined"],
    "answer" : "False",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 2
    },
    {
    "question": "If var a = 1, What do you get when you console.log(a) before declaring variable?",
    "options":["1", "Reference Error", "Undefined", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Undefined",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 3
    },
    {
    "question": "According to JS scope, what happens first when interpreter goes through your code?",
    "options":["Creation Phase", "Execution phase", "Both", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Creation Phase",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 4
    },
    {
    "question": "What does Reference error mean?",
    "options":["Variable not declared", "Variable declared", "Both", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Both",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 5
    },
    {
    "question": "How many scope are there is Javascript?",
    "options":["3", "2", "1", "All of these"],
    "answer" : "2",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 6
    },
    {
    "question": "If I am trying to console.log() a variable before it is delared in ES6 syntax, I get..",
    "options":["Reference Error", "Undefined", "Value of variable", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Reference Error",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 7
    },
    {
    "question": "Where can global variables be accessed?",
    "options":["Globally", "Locally", "Both", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Globally",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 8
    },
    {
    "question": "What controls the scope of variable?",
    "options":["Function location", "Variable location", "Both", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Variable Location",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 9
    },
    {
    "question": "What is scope in Javascript?",
    "options":["Where variables and functions are accessible", "Where functions are accessible", "Where variables are accessible", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Where variables and functions are accessible",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 10
    }

]

export default scope;